

# ZEAO PING (赵平)

#### SENIOR FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

I have 6 years of experience in web development and data science.
I have enough experience in Django, React, Magento 1 & 2, MERN & MEAN stack, and so on. I am convinced of my rich experience and highly skills in web development and data science.

#### **CONTACT**

**EMAIL:** 

zhaoping.dev@gmail.com

**SKYPE** 

live:.cid.b7ea3e4ceb1b7f07

LINKEDIN ACCOUNT

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zhaoping-6187/

**GITHUB ACCOUNT** 

https://github.com/versa-dev

**LANGUAGE** 

English: Fluent

**HOBBIES** 

Football Tennis Badminton Swimming

## **EDUCATION**

**Beijing Jiaotong University, Apr 2012 - Feb 2016**Master's degree of Mathematics and Computer Science

## **EMPLOYMENT DETAILS**

Collins Harper. Full-Stack Web developer May 2020 - present

KR Soft. Senior Full-Stack Engineer

Aug 2018 – Mar 2020

KR Soft. Full-Stack Engineer

Oct 2016 - Aug 2018

Cloudone. Full-Stack Engineer

Apr 2016 - Oct 2016

Upwork.com, Freelancer.com. Full-stack developer & Data scientist

## **SKILLS**

Framework & Library: React.js, Django, Flask, Node.js, Magento, Angular.js, Bubble, Laravel, CodeIgniter, WordPress

**Programming Language :** Javascript, Python, PHP, jQuery, C++,

HTML5, CSS3

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, SQLite, Oracle

Other skills: Mathematics, Jupyter Notebook, Data Science

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Gearo (www.gearo.de)

Technology: Django, Team member: 4.

**Description:** Gearo is a site to provide services to customers who want to sell, rent, or buy the equipments, such as film and photo cameras, lens, tripods, drones, and photo studios. I built this site using only Django framework for less than 2 months with 3 developers.

Evergreen (<u>www.evergreenmidwest.com</u>)

Technology: Magento, Team member: 3.

**Description:** Evergreen is a b2b website and set product price according to customer group. I have created subcategory module, content slide show module and tax module in admin and integrated WordPress module and create PO number order attribute and add in review section of checkout. I have create freight carrier advance shipping method module and use for customer to add freight account and freight carrier.

Weg (www.weg.de)

**Technology:** React.js, **Team member:** 3.

**Description:** Weg is a site to provide very convenient services to travelers who are looking for cheap deals. I have built this project using only React.js for 2 months with 2 other frontend developers. We used Redux to build this website.

Madpaws (<u>www.madpaws.com.au</u>)

Technology: MERN Stack, Team member: 3.

**Description:** This website is for pet services, and I built this website using Node.js for backend and React.js for frontend. My role in this project was project manager and fullstack developer, and other two developers built the frontend. In fact, more than 70% of this project is built by me. I got enough experience in Node.js and React.js in this project.

Boweryfarming (<u>www.boweryfarming.com</u>)

Technology: MEAN Stack, Team member: 4.

**Description:** This website is for fresh vegetable service, and I built this website using Node.js for backend and Angular.js for frontend. My role in this project was backend developer and other 3 developers built the frontend. I got enough experience in MEAN stack technique in this project.

- Crafthues (www.crafthues.co.in)

Technology: Magento, Team member: 2.

**Description:** This is a multi-store ecommerce B2C website. I have worked to create sales report module, integration Magento theme, integrate delivery extension and customize free shipping for particular category in shipment method.

Ovenfresh (<u>www.ovenfresh.in</u>)

**Technology**: Codeigniter, jQuery, Ajax,Mysql. **Team member**: 2.

**Description :** This project is based on online cake delivery and ecommerce website. I have created day1-day2module, sales report module, order expenses module, extra order module, delivery charges module, integrate otp etc.

#### PS:

These projects are just some part of my working projects, and I took part in building number of projects using various kinds of frameworks and languages. I am convinced of my enough experience in web development and data science. I am an honest, passionate, and highly skilled developer with professional level knowledge of mathematics.